[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 41, "question": "Have you heard about that?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 42, "answer": "I haven't heard -- I have seen those same reports but I'm not able to confirm, you know, directly whether that has happened.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 55, "question": "What can you tell me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 56, "answer": "Yes.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 69, "question": "Did you?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 70, "answer": "This crane on 57th Street.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", ":", "DT", "JJS", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "CC", "IN", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NN", "TO", "VB", "RP", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "TO", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 75, "question": "Do you have an update for us on what the plan is for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 76, "answer": "I think they are -- the most recent update I have heard, and that can certainly change, is that although they were going to try to walk up the stairs of the building, that they were not particularly confident that given the high winds that they would be able to necessarily secure it in any way.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "JJ", "VBN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 84, "question": "Are you able to confirm how many people may have lost their lives in New York tonight?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 85, "answer": "The only confirmed fatality I have is the 30-year-old man who was hit by a tree.", "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 96, "question": "How has this been able to happen given we had nearly a week of warning that this huge storm was coming?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "DT", "VBN", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 97, "answer": "Well, looking at the pictures and everything else, what I believe happened is that the crane operator and the supervision on the job did not follow the manufacturer's recommendation.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 110, "question": "Could that happen?", "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 111, "answer": "Absolutely it could happen.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "What are you experiencing?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, Piers, the story here is without question, flooding.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Atlantic City"], "TIME": ["afternoon"]}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "IN", "NN", "RBR", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", ",", "CD", ",", "CD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", ",", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "TO", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "What can you tell me about that and how much of a problem will that be for the mayor, if indeed people do get trapped and potentially lose their lives?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "CC", "WRB", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "IN", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "RB", "NNS", "VBP", "VB", "VBN", "CC", "RB", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "Well, we were talking to the mayor of Atlantic City on air earlier, and I had asked him, I said look, 3:00, 4:00 in the afternoon, what do you do if you haven't left, because the roads have started to become overtopped and he said at that point, if you're not out, stay where you are, get to high ground.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 205, "question": "Have you ever seen anything quite like this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "RB", "VBN", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 206, "answer": "No.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Newark"]}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", ",", "VBN", "CC", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 256, "question": "What is it like where you are?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 257, "answer": "You know, we're experiencing an epic, unprecedented and unpredictable storm in Newark right now.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 268, "question": "Is it simply just stay at home, batten down the hatches and wait?", "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "NN", ",", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 269, "answer": "That's exactly right.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 296, "question": "What do you make of what we're seeing here?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 297, "answer": "Well, it's incredible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "RB", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "How are you fairing over there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "EX", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "Well, we're faring pretty well.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "PRP", "MD", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 338, "question": "From everything you're seeing and reading and hearing tonight, do you think that generally the authorities have prepared well enough for this?", "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 339, "answer": "From what I can see, I believe so.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["southeast Virginia"]}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "NN", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "How bad are things there?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "NNS", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "We're going into day three plus for some of our people down in southeast Virginia.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["New York City"]}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 379, "question": "Are you concerned still?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 380, "answer": "I mean, this is the first disaster I've gone through in New York City.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 480, "question": "What does that do to the financial system?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "IN", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 481, "answer": "I mean, it's pretty incredible, Piers.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 509, "question": "What do you make of it?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 510, "answer": "Well, obviously we knew this was possible.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 519, "question": "Ali, what can you tell me?", "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 520, "answer": "Yes, take a look at this.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", ",", "RB", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 543, "question": "What do you think that will do to the financial markets?", "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "MD", "VB", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 544, "answer": "Well, it's very interesting, not only is this hurricane -- Super Storm Sandy stealing Halloween from some people, the end of the month is very important worldwide for traders, for fund managers, for hedge fund managers, because everyone is judged monthly on their performance.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121029pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 553, "question": "And if so, what impact can this all have on the election?", "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "RB", ",", "WDT", "NN", "MD", "DT", "DT", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 554, "answer": "Well, generally speaking, the measurement for the job numbers is taken in a week and it's earlier.", "question_ne_tagged": {}}]